<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Fujiao Ji</title>
        <link>http://fujiaoji.github.io/</link>
        <description>This is my cool site</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 13:07:46 -0500</lastBuildDate>
            <atom:link href="http://fujiaoji.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
    <title>PhishFarm: A Scalable Framework for Measuring the Effectiveness of Evasion Techniques Against Browser Phishing Blacklists</title>
    <link>http://fujiaoji.github.io/posts/2023-2-23/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 13:07:46 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://fujiaoji.github.io/posts/2023-2-23/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Research Question We know that blacklists are effective when they function as intended, but is this always the case? Do blacklists offer adequate protection against phishers’ evasion efforts such as cloaking, or are phishers launching attacks with impunity? We focus on answering these questions in the rest of this paper.
Abstract PhishFarm: testing resilence of anti-phishing entities and browser blacklists to attackers&rsquo; evasion.
Introduction Weakness of blacklist: reactive. So attackers use cloaking technique to avoid or delay detection.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>PhishTime: Continuous Longitudinal Measurement of the Effectiveness of Anti-phishing Blacklist</title>
    <link>http://fujiaoji.github.io/posts/2023-2-22/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 09:31:48 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://fujiaoji.github.io/posts/2023-2-22/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Question: How they test which web can pass or not pass the blacklist??? How they design the experiment 2. Background Spearphishing: concentrate on a specific group or individuals Large-scale phishing: targets a wide range of victims and allows fishers to profit through volume
2.1 phishing attacks Typical phishing attack: appearance similar to the legistimate website.
2.2 anti-phishing blacklists Evasion Tech: Weakness of blacklist: they are reactive. Phishers capitalize on the time gap between a phishing website’s deployment and its subsequent blacklisting, and may increase their return-on-investment (ROI) by prolonging this gap]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Reading Adversarial Papers for Project2</title>
    <link>http://fujiaoji.github.io/posts/adversarialpaper/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 13:31:49 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://fujiaoji.github.io/posts/adversarialpaper/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Pixle: a fast and effective black-box attack based on rearranging pixels ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Pretrained model for logos or icons</title>
    <link>http://fujiaoji.github.io/posts/2023-2-6/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 09:47:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://fujiaoji.github.io/posts/2023-2-6/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Logo Detection Using Deep Learning with Pretrained CNN Models [1] What:
Use pre-trained object detection models to enhance the performance of logo detection tasks when only a portion of labeled training images taken in truthful context is obtainable, evading wide manual classification costs In this paper, RCNN, FRCNN and RetinaNet were used for logo detection (In this paper, there is a comarason of different image methods, deserving read) How Use pretrained model to get features: 1) RetinaNet, 2) Faster R-CNN Other Information]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Phishing Detection via Identification of Website Identity</title>
    <link>http://fujiaoji.github.io/posts/phishing-detection-via-identification-of-website-identity/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 11:12:52 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://fujiaoji.github.io/posts/phishing-detection-via-identification-of-website-identity/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[1. Paper summary The authors proposed an anti-phishing method to protect Internet users from the phishing attacks. Specifically, they first obtained screenshots, then segmented them to get the logos. After that, they utilized Google image database to search and return keywords. Next, they used the keywords to search again, then compare domain name between the query website and the second search domain name.
2. Background Earth Movers Distance (EMD): Fu et al.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>How to Subplot Pictures to One Figure</title>
    <link>http://fujiaoji.github.io/posts/how-to-subplot-pictures-to-one-figure/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 16:22:25 -0600</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://fujiaoji.github.io/posts/how-to-subplot-pictures-to-one-figure/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Subplot pictures in one figure:
from PIL import Image import matplotlib.pyplot as plt row_length = 5 column_length = 5 for i in range(row_length): for j in range(column_length): plt.subplot(row_length, column_length, i*5+j+1) im = Image.open(&#34;a.png&#34;) if j == 0: plt.ylabel(&#34;XXX&#34;) plt.yticks([]) plt.xticks([]) plt.imshow(im, cmap=&#39;gray&#39;) plt.tight_layout() plt.savefig(&#34;test.png&#34;) ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Useful Tips When Writing Codes on Vscode</title>
    <link>http://fujiaoji.github.io/posts/useful-tips-when-writing-codes-on-vscode/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 16:28:09 -0600</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://fujiaoji.github.io/posts/useful-tips-when-writing-codes-on-vscode/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[ Zip a folder: zip -r destination_folder_name.zip source_folder_name Unzip a folder: unzip source_folder_name.zip -d ./destination_folder_name/. Specifically, ./ means current directory, ../ means parent directory, ~ means home directory, / means root directory. Do not use / directory !!! In linux, terminal, etc., create a new file, touch XXX.cpp In terminal, command + T will help you open a new window ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>VisualPhishNet Zero Day PhishingWebsite Detection by Visual Similarity</title>
    <link>http://fujiaoji.github.io/posts/visualphishnet-zero-day-phishingwebsite-detection-by-visual-similarity/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 22:34:43 -0600</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://fujiaoji.github.io/posts/visualphishnet-zero-day-phishingwebsite-detection-by-visual-similarity/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I. Introduction 1. Situation of anti-phishing method Phishing webpages try to deceive paper by high visual similarity between phishing webpage and legistimate ones. Some methods maintain a list of commonly attack pages (domain name and their screenshots). However, these methods have limitations: 1) list is small; 2) attackers can bypass detection by crafting partially similar phishing pages with different background pictures.
2. Contributions of this paper Present dataset of VisualPhish, 155 trust websites with 9363 pages.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Inferring Phishing Intention via Webpage Appearance and Dynamics a Deep Vision Based Approach</title>
    <link>http://fujiaoji.github.io/posts/inferring-phishing-intention-via-webpage-appearance-and-dynamics-a-deep-vision-based-approach/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 12:47:05 -0600</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://fujiaoji.github.io/posts/inferring-phishing-intention-via-webpage-appearance-and-dynamics-a-deep-vision-based-approach/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I. Introduction 1. Situation of anti-phishing method Manually verified anti-phishing blacklist: use dynamic blacklists to track reported phishing URLs. eg. Google Classification-based methods: trained from collecting phishing dataset, perform binary classification Reference-based methods: detecting phishing attacks by referencing a set of representations of well-known brands. 2. Challenges The blacklists and collected phishing webpages used for training become obsolete very quickly, resulting in a never-ending cat-and-mouse game between phishing attacks and defenses that are based on blacklists/classification.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>UsefulInformation</title>
    <link>http://fujiaoji.github.io/posts/usefulinformation/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 12:23:49 -0600</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://fujiaoji.github.io/posts/usefulinformation/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[From paper &ldquo;Image similarity using Deep CNN and Curriculum Learning&rdquo; Typical image descriptors: SIFT, LBP, CNN embedding’s etc; From paper Inferring Phishing Intention via Webpage Appearance and Dynamics: A Deep Vision Based Approach&quot; VisualPhishNet[1] use screenshots [1] [2] and logos [3] [4] [5] as the reference representations of target websites Logo2K+ dataset [6] From paper VisualPhishNet Zero Day PhishingWebsite Detection by Visual Similarity SIFT, SURF, HOG, CCH, ORB, etc. Logo extraction paper: [7] Reading, [8] Reference [1] SaharAbdelnabi, Katharina Krombholz, and Mario Fritz VisualPhishNet: Zero-Day Phishing Website Detection by Visual Similarity.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
