<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>ReadPaper - Tag - Fujiao Ji</title>
        <link>http://fujiaoji.github.io/tags/readpaper/</link>
        <description>ReadPaper - Tag - Fujiao Ji</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 13:07:46 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://fujiaoji.github.io/tags/readpaper/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Reading: URL and Blacklist Project</title>
    <link>http://fujiaoji.github.io/posts/reading-papers-for-url-and-blacklist-project/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 13:07:46 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://fujiaoji.github.io/posts/reading-papers-for-url-and-blacklist-project/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Reading: An Analysis of Phishing Blacklists: Google Safe Browsing, OpenPhish, and PhishTank Abstract Focus on Google safe browsing, OpenPhish, PhishTank Intro Phishing blacklist are defense strategy that aim to protect people from phishing attacks. Blacklist contain known phishing URLs. These blacklists need update quickly and regularly to protect users. Urls should be removed from the blacklist when they are no longer a threat.
Reading: PhishFarm: A Scalable Framework for Measuring the Effectiveness of Evasion Techniques Against Browser Phishing Blacklists Research Question We know that blacklists are effective when they function as intended, but is this always the case?]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Reading Papers for Phishing Project</title>
    <link>http://fujiaoji.github.io/posts/reading-papers-for-phishing-project/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 12:47:05 -0600</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://fujiaoji.github.io/posts/reading-papers-for-phishing-project/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Reading: 2021-USENIX-Phishpedia: A Hybrid Deep Learning Based Approach to Visually Identify Phishing Webpages Code Research Question How Thought Reading: 2021-USENIX-Inferring Phishing Intention via Webpage Appearance and Dynamics a Deep Vision Based Approach Code I. Introduction 1. Situation of anti-phishing method 2. Challenges 3. Main Contribution II. PhishIntention: Design and Development 1. Technical Challenges: 2. Steps Step 1: Abstract Webpage Layout Detection (need labeled data). Step 2: OCR-aided Brand Recognition. Step 3: CRP Classification.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
