<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>ReadPaper - Tag - Fujiao Ji</title>
        <link>http://fujiaoji.github.io/tags/readpaper/</link>
        <description>ReadPaper - Tag - Fujiao Ji</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 13:07:46 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://fujiaoji.github.io/tags/readpaper/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Reading: URL and Blacklist Project</title>
    <link>http://fujiaoji.github.io/posts/reading-papers-for-url-and-blacklist-project/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 13:07:46 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://fujiaoji.github.io/posts/reading-papers-for-url-and-blacklist-project/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Reading: An Analysis of Phishing Blacklists: Google Safe Browsing, OpenPhish, and PhishTank Abstract Focus on Google safe browsing, OpenPhish, PhishTank Intro Phishing blacklist are defense strategy that aim to protect people from phishing attacks. Blacklist contain known phishing URLs. These blacklists need update quickly and regularly to protect users. Urls should be removed from the blacklist when they are no longer a threat. Add again when threat again.
What they have done: study 3 blacklists: GSB, PT, and OP, to determine uptake, dropout, typical lifetimes, and any overlap of URLs in these blacklists.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Reading: Phishing Project</title>
    <link>http://fujiaoji.github.io/posts/reading-papers-for-phishing-project/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 12:47:05 -0600</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://fujiaoji.github.io/posts/reading-papers-for-phishing-project/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Reading: 2021-USENIX-Phishpedia: A Hybrid Deep Learning Based Approach to Visually Identify Phishing Webpages Code Available
Research Question To address two prominent technical challenges in phishing identification, i.e., (i) accurate recognition of identity logos on webpage screenshots, and (ii) matching logo variants of the same brands.
How Dividing the phishing identification problem into 1) identify logo recognition [use the object detection] and 2) brand recognition problem [use Siamese model].
Object detection: generates a set of bounding boxes to annotate the position and size of the objects on the image.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
